A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (L-Z), Accession 2021:051 FA1790
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts, 2007-2017; 3
  - The Tower Foundation of San Jose University - Mendelssohn's Elijah Production (2016-52599) (Box 66, Folder 864)
  - Trustees of the University of Pennsylvania - Contemporary Art 101 (2016-52618) (Box 67, Folder 886)
  - Tubman African American Museum, Inc. - The Pan African Festival of Georgia (2016-52695) (Box 68, Folder 893)
  - Tuesday Musical Association - 125th Anniversary Season, Clara I. Knight (2011-0295), 2009-2013 (Box 68, Folder 894)
  - Two Fish Design - SubZero Festival 2015 (2015-50843), 2013-2015 (Box 68, Folder 900)
  - University Cultural Center Association - Dlectricity (2012-0256), 2010-2013 (Box 69, Folder 910)
    A free nightime contemporary art festival featuring site-specific installations of light, 3D video mapping, sound, and performance in Midtown Detroit's Woodward Corridor.
  - University of Miami - The Marvin and Ruth Sackner Artists' Books and Concrete Poetry Collection (2017-54354), 2016-2017 (Box 71, Folder 930)
  - University of Miami - Shelton Berg, Knight Art Champion 2017 Designation (2017-55370) (Box 71, Folder 931)
  - University of Miami - Sebastian Spring, Knight Art Champion 2017 Designation (2017-55383) (Box 71, Folder 932)
  - University of Maryland - DeVos Institute: Capacity Building in Greater San Jose (2014-49505), 2013-2017 (Box 71, Folder 933)
  - University of Miami - Public Art Project, Sea Level Rise (2015-50650) (Box 71, Folder 936)
  - University of Miami - Knight Recital Hall (2015-50784), 2013-2015 (Box 71, Folder 937)
  - University of Miami - Henry Mancini Institute: Outbound, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0274), 2010-2014 (Box 72, Folder 943)
  - University of the Arts - Pre-Seed Funding, Mentorships and Workshops (2012-0096), 2010-2014 (Box 75, Folder 968)
  - University of Wynwood, Inc. - Campbell McGrath, Knight Art Champion 2017 Designation (2017-55380) (Box 75, Folder 971)
  - Urgent, Inc. - South Florida's Negro League Baseball Team Murals in Dorsey Park, Overtown (2012-0401), 2012-2014 (Box 76, Folder 980)
  - US Biennial, Inc. - Prospect.4: The Lotus in Spite of the Swamp, Odili Donald Odita (2017-54596), 2014-2017 (Box 76, Folder 983)
  - Village of Arts and Humanities - Interactive Scavenger Hunts by Local Artists (2012-0097), 2010-2015 (Box 77, Folder 994)
  - Village of Arts and Humanities - The Urban Experience: Artist-in-Residence Program (2012-3335), 2011-2014 (Box 77, Folder 995)
  - Village of Arts and Humanities - Shooters (2016-52717) (Box 77, Folder 996)
    A program that challenges emerging filmmakers to create high quality documentary shorts in Philadelphia in a six-week period.
  - Vizcaya Museum and Gardens Trust Inc. - Enhancing the Vizcaya Experience through 3D Technologies (2017-54064) (Box 77, Folder 998)
  - Visual Philosophy, LLC - Instructor Exchange Residency (2016-52636) (Box 77, Folder 1002)
  - Vox Populi, Inc. - First Fridays Philadelphia (2014-50152), 2013-2016 (Box 77, Folder 1005)
  - Wall Poems - Goodyear Arts Residency (2016-52701) (Box 78, Folder 1011)
  - Wall Poems - Wall Poems, Charlotte (2015-50630), 2013-2015 (Box 78, Folder 1012)
  - The Wilma Theater - The Wilma Hothouse (2015-50838), 2015-2016 (Box 81, Folder 1044)
  - The Wilma Theater - Master Classes (2012-0098), 2010-2013 (Box 81, Folder 1045)
  - WLRN Inc. - ArtStreetMiami.org, Knight Arts Challenge (2010-0277), 2010-2011 (Box 81, Folder 1049)
  - WRTI - MusicMakers (2012-2510), 2011-2013 (Box 82, Folder 1056)
  - XOXO Performance - #Cake (2016-52634), 2013-2016 (Box 82, Folder 1061)
- Technology and Media Innovation, 2011-2017; 4
  The Technology and Media Innovation program focuses on investing in technology that impacts the way people interact with news and information. This program area overlaps with the Journalism and Media Innovation program but was referred to as "Technology and Media Innovation" during the time of the grants in this collection.
  - Local Projects, LLC - MyCity Pre-Development Market Research (2015-51290), 2012-2016 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Marshall-Whyte School of Law Foundation - Revive My Vote (2015-51008), 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    Increase civic information literacy among formerly incarcerated Virginians on a nonpartisan basis by developing a mobile app and website to educate citizens about the voting rights restoration process and partnering with government agencies to improve citizen engagement.
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Public Library Innovation Exchange (2016-53267) (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Decentralized Publishing on the Web (2015-51640) (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Maxwell Galka - FOIA Mapper (2015-52007) (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Media Public - MediaPublic (2015-51236), 2013-2015 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    A platform that allows public media organizations to recruit new types of volunteers.
  - Metropolitan Area Planning Council - Neighborhood Drawing Tool (2015-50806), 2013-2015 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Miami Foundation - AI Fund Coordinator (2017-54408) (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - Miami Foundation - Prototype Fund Fees (2017-55247) (Box 13, Folder 177)
  - Miami Foundation - Prototype Fees (2016-53020), 2013-2016 (Box 13, Folder 182)
  - Miami Foundation - Ethics and Governance of Artificial Intelligence Fund (2016-53390) (Box 14, Folder 189)
  - Miami Foundation - Data Equity for Main Street: Bringing Open Data Home through Local Libraries (2015-51934), 2013-2017 (Box 16, Folder 209)
  - Monday Note SAS - News Quality Scoring (2017-54391) (Box 25, Folder 306)
  - Museum of New Mexico Foundation - Indigenous Digital Archive (2016-52832) (Box 26, Folder 324)
  - National Freedom of Information Coalition - Open Government Mobile Transparency Training and Support (2014-49648), 2012-2014 (Box 28, Folder 352)
  - New American Foundation - New America, New York (2014-49887), 2011-2014 (Box 30, Folder 372)
  - New Museum of Contemporary Art - Museum Tech Incubation Track (2017-53877) (Box 30, Folder 382)
  - New York Metropolitan Reference and Research Library Agency - Culture In Transit (2015-50377), 2012-2016 (Box 32, Folder 403)
  - New York Public Library, Astor, Lenox, and Tilden Foundations - NYC Space/Time Directory (2015-50374), 2015-2017 (Box 32, Folder 405)
  - New York Public Radio - Judge Your Judges (2015-51101), 2011-2015 (Box 32, Folder 408)
  - New York University - RevEx: A Data Visualization Tool to Find Stories in Millions of Internet Reviews (2015-51984), 2015-2016 (Box 33, Folder 414)
  - New America Foundation - TechCongress Congressional Innovation Fellowship (2015-51812), 2013-2015 (Box 33, Folder 416)
  - Ohio University - TrollBusters (2015-50829) (Box 36, Folder 449)
  - One Degree - One App (2015-51456), 2015-2017 (Box 36, Folder 453)
  - Online Computer Library Center, Inc. - Wikipedia and Libraries (2016-52990), 2016-2017 (Box 36, Folder 456)
  - Open Source Election Technology Foundation - VoteStream Beta, Election Results System (2014-49092) (Box 38, Folder 477)
  - Orbmedia, Inc. - Weighing the Wisdom of the Crowd (2015-51948), 2013-2017 (Box 38, Folder 480)
  - Orlando Sentinel Communications Company, LLC - Tabs on Tallahassee (2015-51043), 2013-2015 (Box 38, Folder 481)
    An API that shows the voting records of Florida Legislators.
  - Participatory Politics Foundation - AskTem.io Prototype Fund (2014-49634), 2012-2014 (Box 39, Folder 487)
  - Peer 2 Peer University Inc. - Expanding the Learning Circle Program, Knight News Challenge (2016-53558), 2016-2017 (Box 40, Folder 497)
  - Pennsylvania State University - Digging DEEP: A Digital Extension Education Portal for Community Growth (2016-52833), 2015-2016 (Box 40, Folder 501)
  - Periscopic - ChartCheck (2017-54554) (Box 40, Folder 507)
  - Philadelphia Public Access Corporation - People's Media Collections (2016-52822), 2016-2017 (Box 43, Folder 531)
  - Platform - Platform Summit and Platform Network (2015-50992), 2013-2017 (Box 44, Folder 557)
  - Portland Press Herald - News Inequality Project (2017-54379) (Box 45, Folder 564)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - All the Places Personal Data Goes (2016-52102), 2015-2016 (Box 46, Folder 577)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Can I Fair Use It? Crowdsourcing Fair Use Knowledge (2016-52855) (Box 46, Folder 578)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Library Innovation Mentorship Program (2016-52946), 2015-2016 (Box 46, Folder 580)
  - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Responsive Communities (2016-53486), 2016-2017 (Box 46, Folder 581)
  - Project TF - Capital Growth Campaign (2017-54816), 2016-2017 (Box 46, Folder 588)
  - Project TF - Code2040 Organizational and Programmatic Support (2016-53253), 2016-2017 (Box 46, Folder 589)
  - Project TF - Code2040 (2015-51738), 2013-2017 (Box 46, Folder 591)
    To suport professional development for Black and Latino media netrepreneurs and innovators working in the technology industry.
  - Prometheus Radio Project - LPFM Radio Impact Maps (2015-51673) (Box 47, Folder 592)
  - PRX Inc. - Reimagining Radiotopia (2015-50411), 2013-2017 (Box 47, Folder 596)
  - PRX Inc. - Kickstarter Project (2014-50004) (Box 47, Folder 597)
  - Public Library of Charlotte and Mecklenburg County - Creating a Civic Destination (2017-53831) (Box 47, Folder 603)
  - Quartz - Mapquery (2015-51682), 2013-2015 (Box 48, Folder 609)
    Acquisition, cleaning, merging, and refining of geographic data to improve the production of data maps.
  - The Regents of the University of California, Santa Cruz - Breaking Filter Bubbles in Science Journalism (2017-54390) (Box 49, Folder 626)
  - Rhizome Communications Inc. - Webrecorder (2015-51935) (Box 49, Folder 635)
    Tool to archive dynamic web content.
  - Richland County Public Library - Customer Engagement and Participation Tracking (2017-53793) (Box 49, Folder 638)
  - Robert James Steinert III - Open Pipe Kit (2014-50255), 2012-2015 (Box 50, Folder 643)
  - Run Hop - Hudson App (2015-51647), 2013-2015 (Box 51, Folder 651)
  - Samaruddin Stewart - Verified Pixel Project (2015-50808), 2013-2015 (Box 52, Folder 665)
    Prototype to help newsroom verify user-generated content.
  - San Francisco Public Press - Support of Pedal-Powered News (2017-54152) (Box 52, Folder 670)
    Market and distribute print publications via bike carriers.
  - San Jose Public Library - Privacy Literacy: It's No Secret (2014-50228) (Box 53, Folder 683)
  - Satchel LLC - Satchel (2015-52010) (Box 53, Folder 689)
    A tool to increase discovery and sharing of audio content such as on-demand audio and podcasts.
  - Shift Design, Inc. - Our Story: Content, Collections, and Impact in Rural America (2016-52978), 2016-2017 (Box 54, Folder 705)
  - Simiary - Pteraform (2015-51681), 2013-2015 (Box 55, Folder 718)
    A platform that enables users to geographically visualize and interact with information related to a search query.
  - Singularity Education Group - HUB's Open Source Virtual Research Assistant for Writers and Journalists (2015-51973), 2013-2015 (Box 55, Folder 719)
  - Southwest Harbor Public Library - Relationship Builder for Omeka (2016-53648), 2016-2017 (Box 58, Folder 759)
  - Stephanie Singer - Prototype Data Quality Uplift for Government (2016-52052), 2013-2016 (Box 59, Folder 775)
  - The Steve Fund - Operational and Programmatic Support, Crisis Text Line (2016-53176), 2013-2017 (Box 59, Folder 777)
  - The Steve Fund - Build Capacity (2016-53183), 2013-2017 (Box 60, Folder 780)
  - StoryCorps, Inc. - Technology Infrastructure (2017-54706), 2015-2017 (Box 60, Folder 781)
  - StoryCorps, Inc. - App Development (2015-50926), 2015-2016 (Box 60, Folder 782)
  - StoryScape - Literacy, Art, Technology, and Community (2016-52852), 2013-2016 (Box 60, Folder 786)
  - Syracuse University - SpeakEZ (2015-51218) (Box 61, Folder 806)
    A mobile phone-based voice system for refugees.
  - Tech Gypsies LLC - Federal Agency Dataset Adoption (2015-51217) (Box 63, Folder 823)
  - Temple University - Future Proofing Civic Data (2016-52854) (Box 63, Folder 838)
  - This American Life - Shortcut (2017-53993) (Box 64, Folder 848)
    App to clip and share podcasts online.
  - This American Life - Audioshare Tool (2015-52023), 2013-2015 (Box 64, Folder 850)
  - Times Publishing Company - Facts Matter, PolitiFact (2017-54410) (Box 65, Folder 858)
  - The Tor Project, Inc. - The Library Freedom Project (2014-50256) (Box 65, Folder 862)
  - Trustees of Boston University - Social Media Interventions to Reduce the Spread of Misinformation (2017-54495) (Box 66, Folder 869)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - Security Force Monitor (2016-52101), 2014-2017 (Box 66, Folder 875)
  - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - CAT Conflict Analysis Toolbox (2015-50313), 2013-2015 (Box 66, Folder 876)
  - Trustees of Dartmouth College - Unlocking Film Libraries for Discovery and Search (2016-52835), 2014-2016 (Box 67, Folder 884)
  - University of Kansas Center for Research Inc. - InfoCertainty (2014-49933), 2012-2014 (Box 70, Folder 926)
  - University of Miami - Open Privacy Project (2015-51981) (Box 71, Folder 938)
  - University of Miami - Digital Learning Training (2014-49764), 2011-2016 (Box 71, Folder 941)
  - University of Washington - Calling Bullshit in the Age of Fake News (2017-54392) (Box 75, Folder 969)
  - University of Washington - SeaGlass: Bringing Transparency to Cell Phone Surveillance (2015-51996) (Box 75, Folder 970)
  - Urban Affairs Coalition - Sharp Insight (2015-51003), 2012-2016 (Box 75, Folder 975)
    To increase civic information literacy among black males in Philadelphia on a nonpartisan basis by training barbers on how to educate their communities on issues relating to civic engagement and restoration of rights.
  - Univision Communications, Inc. - Immigration Lab (2017-54414) (Box 75, Folder 976)
  - Ushahidi, Inc. - Ping App (2014-49657) (Box 76, Folder 981)
    An emergency check-in tool for groups during a crisis or disaster with support for low-tech phones.
  - Veracity.ai - Disrupting Ad-Supported Online Misinformation (2017-54418) (Box 77, Folder 992)
  - Vocativ, LLC - Dataproofer (2015-51675) (Box 77, Folder 1003)
    A desktop app that identifies basic errors within datasets before reporting or visualization begins.
  - Wesleyan University - Media Project (2016-52206), 2013-2016 (Box 79, Folder 1027)
  - West Virginia University Foundation Inc. - Reed College of Media Innovator-in-Residence Program (2014-49779), 2012-2016 (Box 79, Folder 1032)
  - When It Changed Inc. - Are.na / Pilgrim (2015-51668), 2013-2015 (Box 80, Folder 1034)
  - Xavier Damman - Tipbox (2014-50244), 2012-2015 (Box 82, Folder 1060)
    A tool to allow journalists to receive encrypted emails without requiring their sources to have encryption knowledge.
  - Young Mie Kim - Silent Targeting, Loud Democracy: Microtargeting in Election Campaigns (2015-52006), 2013-2016 (Box 82, Folder 1064)
- Learning and Impact, 2014-2017; 5
  The Learning and Impact program focuses on assessment and research within the Foundation. Its goal is to review investments to determine how they are impacting and promoting the goals of the organization.
  - Media Impact Funders, Inc. - 2016 Membership and Impact Measurement (2016-53513) (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - National Opinion Research Center - Trust in News among Young Adults (2017-55079) (Box 29, Folder 360)
  - New York University - Social Media and Political Participation (SMaPP) Laboratory (2017-54053) (Box 32, Folder 412)
  - The Pew Charitable Trusts - Trust, Media, and Democracy (2017-54145), 2015-2017 (Box 41, Folder 510)
  - Social Science Research Council - Anxieties of Democracy Media Project (2016-53491), 2015-2017 (Box 55, Folder 725)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Identifying the Perspective of Snapchat Users in the 2016 Election (2016-53210), 2014-2016 (Box 74, Folder 964)
  - University of Texas, Austin - Elections Cohort Outcomes, Knight News Challenge (2016-53279) (Box 74, Folder 965)
  - University of Texas, Austin - The Engaging News Project (2015-51667), 2014-2015 (Box 75, Folder 967)
- Other, 2002-2017; 6
  This series includes grants that fall outside of the Knight Foundation's primary program areas. Grants are arranged into groupings that represent the Trustee-Advised Grant Program, the Emergency/Impact Fund, Communications, and Membership.
  - Trustee-Advised Grant Program, 2004-2017; 1
    - Macon Georgia Cherry Blossom Festival Inc. - Street Party (Olson) (2017-53847) (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Macon Georgia Cherry Blossom Festival Inc. - Taiko Japanese Drummers (Olson) (2014-48022) (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Macon Rescue Mission - New Signage (Olson) (2014-49540) (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Macon Symphony Orchestra - Symphonie Fantastique (Olson) (2017-54156) (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Macon Symphony Orchestra - April 25, 2015 Celebration (Olson) (2014-49576) (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Macon Volunteer Clinic Inc. - New Building (Olson) (2017-54590) (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - List Visual Arts Centre (Ito) (2017-54069), 2015-2017 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - General Operating Support (Ito) (2014-48634) (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Massachusetts Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, Angell Animal Shelter - General Operating Support (Ito) (2017-55342) (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Medcen Foundation Inc. - Children's Hospital Golf Classic (Olson) (2017-54013), 2011-2017 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Medcen Foundation Inc. - Children's Hospital Celebrity Classic (Olson) (2014-48516), 2011-2014 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - The Mentor's Project of Bibb County - General Support (Olson) (2017-54149) (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Miami Art Museum of Dade County Association - General Operating Support (Ibarguen) (2013-47794), 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Miami Art Museum of Dade County Association - Fundraising for African American Art, Perez Art Museum (2014-49005) (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Miami City Ballet - General Operating Support (Ibarguen) (2014-49753) (Box 10, Folder 134)
    - National Foundation for the Advancement in the Arts - Support the Development of Young Artists (Powell) (2014-48527), 2011-2014 (Box 28, Folder 351)
    - National Urban Squash and Education Association, Inc. - General Support (Palfrey) (2014-49774) (Box 29, Folder 365)
    - New England Baseball Club Inc. - Scholarship Support, New England Ruffnecks (Palfrey) (2017-54402) (Box 30, Folder 373)
    - New England Baseball Club Inc. - Scholarships (Palfrey) (2014-50142) (Box 30, Folder 374)
    - The New School, Journalism and Design Program - General Operating Support (Steiger) (2016-52955) (Box 33, Folder 417)
    - North Carolina Arboretum - Cultivating a Living Treasure (Baker) (2004-0124) (Box 34, Folder 429)
    - The Oak Clinic - General Operating Support (Briggs) (2014-48503), 2012-2014 (Box 36, Folder 445)
    - PEN American Center Inc. - General Operating Support (Steiger) (2017-54774) (Box 39, Folder 495)
    - President and Fellows of Harvard College - Berkman Center for Internet and Society (Palfrey) (2017-55281) (Box 46, Folder 576)
    - Purdue University - Education Support (E. Roe Stamps IV) (2014-49729) (Box 47, Folder 605)
    - Queens University of Charlotte - James L. Knight Scholarship Fund, School of Communication (Crane) (2014-48461), 2011-2014 (Box 48, Folder 613)
    - Rockend Inc. - Summer Art Program, Rockend Art Barn (Austen) (2017-55365) (Box 50, Folder 645)
    - Rotary Camp for Children with Special Needs Inc. - Disabilities Camp Program (Considine) (2017-53977) (Box 51, Folder 650)
    - St. Martin de Porres Academy - General Operating Support in Honor of William T. Kosturko (Ibarguen) (2013-47910), 2011-2013 (Box 51, Folder 653)
    - St. Francis Hospital and Medical Center - Comprehensive Women's Health Center (Borges) (2014-48716), 2011-2014 (Box 51, Folder 654)
    - The Salvation Army, Charlotte - General Support (Neill) (2007-0139) (Box 52, Folder 664)
    - Silicon Valley Community Foundation - Cambia (Ito) (2014-49154) (Box 54, Folder 713)
    - Southern Methodist University - Dr. Gerald Turner Leadership Award (2016-52563) (Box 57, Folder 748)
      To contribute to the Dean's Discretionary Fund for the Simmon's School of Education and Human Development, in honor of Dr. Turner's leadership as co-chair of the Knight Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics.
    - SquashBusters, Inc. - Academics and Sports in Lawrence, MA (Palfrey) (2017-55284) (Box 59, Folder 768)
    - SquashBusters, Inc. - Squash and Education in Lawrence, MA (Palfrey) (2014-49775) (Box 59, Folder 769)
    - The Steve Fund - Health of Young People of Color (Bell-Rose) (2017-53878) (Box 59, Folder 776)
    - Summit Education Initiative - General Operating Support (Briggs) (2014-48505), 2011-2014 (Box 60, Folder 793)
    - Teach for America Inc. - Charlotte Teachers (Nelson) (2014-49921) (Box 62, Folder 812)
    - Teach for America Inc. - Education in Charleston (Nelson) (2017-55299) (Box 62, Folder 816)
    - Thompson Child and Family Focus - Early Childhood Services (Crane) (2014-48463), 2011-2014 (Box 64, Folder 851)
    - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - Graduate School of Journalism (Steiger) (2017-54769) (Box 66, Folder 873)
    - Trustees of Columbia University in the City of New York - Knight-Bagehot Fellowship (Steiger) (2017-54773) (Box 66, Folder 874)
    - Tuskegee Airmen, Inc. - Memorial Gift in Honor of John W. Rogers Sr. (2014-48096) (Box 68, Folder 895)
    - The Umbrella Community Arts Center - General Support (Austen) (2017-55363) (Box 68, Folder 902)
    - United Way of Miami-Dade - Community Support (Rodriguez) (2017-55319) (Box 69, Folder 906)
    - United Way of Summit County - Education Strategies (Mayer) (2017-54617) (Box 69, Folder 907)
    - United Way of Summit County - Transformation Strategy (Mayer) (2016-53502) (Box 69, Folder 908)
    - University of Akron Foundation - College of Business Administration (Briggs) (2014-48504), 2011-2014 (Box 69, Folder 911)
    - University of Akron - Scholarship Funds (Considine) (2017-53973) (Box 69, Folder 912)
    - University of Akron - Media Immersion Program (Crutchfield) (2014-49571) (Box 69, Folder 915)
    - University of Florida Foundation - Powell Gene Therapy Endowment (Powell) (2014-48496) (Box 70, Folder 922)
    - University of Maryland - Crohn's and Colitis Center, School of Medicine (Rodriguez) (2017-55321) (Box 71, Folder 929)
    - University of Miami - General Operating Support (Ibarguen) (2017-54439), 2016-2017 (Box 71, Folder 934)
    - University of Miami - Newman Alumni Loyalty Challenge (Powell) (2014-48528), 2011-2014 (Box 71, Folder 939)
    - University of Miami - Ophthalmology Academic Fund (Powell) (2014-48529), 2011-2014 (Box 71, Folder 940)
    - Virginia-Maryland College of Veterinary Medicine - Stamps Scholars Program (E. Roe Stamps, IV) (2017-54038) (Box 77, Folder 997)
    - Wesleyan University - General Operating Support (Ibarguen) (2013-47793), 2014 (Box 79, Folder 1028)
    - WITNESS, Inc. - General Operating Support (Ito) (2017-55340) (Box 81, Folder 1048)
    - Youth Development Organization, Inc. - Self-Motivated Learners and Leaders (Palfrey) (2017-54403) (Box 82, Folder 1067)
    - Youngstown State University Foundation - The News Outlet (Briggs) (2014-48506), 2012-2014 (Box 82, Folder 1068)
  - Emergency/Impact Fund, 2009-2017; 2
    - Miami Children's Initiative, Inc. - Feasibility Study for the Safe Harbor Concept, Marvin Dunn (2015-50860) (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Miami Dade Chamber of Commerce Foundation, Inc. - General Support (2015-50913) (Box 11, Folder 140)